（上条(かみじょう)）
学園都市を離れた夏の海で―
At a summer beach far away from Academy City,
わたくし 上条当麻(とうま)は
家族との再会を果たす
I, Kamijyo Touma, am having a reunion with my family.
A magic spell known as "Angel Fall" has befallen us though.
そんな俺たちを
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)なる魔術が襲った
ロシア教会の
ミーシャ＝クロイツェフ
Misha Kreuzhev of the Russian Orthodox Church,
そして 神裂火織(かんざき かおり)と
共に現れた土御門元春(つちみかど もとはる)
and Tsuchimikado Motoharu,
who appeared with Kanzaki Kaori,
彼もまた 何を隠そう―
also a member of Necessarius.
必要悪の教会(ネセサリウス)の
メンバーだったのである
...Wait, what?!?!
…て なに！？
#16 Kamijyo Touya
Father
（土御門）
いや　だから カミやん
～♪
C'mon, Kami-yan.
（土御門）
俺も 必要悪の教会(ネセサリウス)の一員ぜよ
I'm also a member of Necessarius.
必要悪の教会(ネセサリウス)って… じゃ お前も…
Necessarius?!
Then, you're a...
Yeah, a magician.
（土御門）ああ 魔術師だ
（上条）でも…
But...
"There's no way a magician can be in Academy City", eh?
学園都市に
魔術師がいるわけないってか？
考えてもみろよ カミやん
Think about it, Kami-yan.
"Science" and "magic" are enemies.
科学は魔術の敵だぜ　だったら―
Then an agent or two sneaking into enemy territory... isn't that shocking, right?
敵地に潜り込んでる工作員の
１人や２人
いたって おかしくないだろう
工作員…
Agent...
A spy, if you will.
（土御門）
つまりはスパイってこと
カミやんにまつわる大概のことは
知ってるぜよ
I know of most things surrounding you, Kami-yan.
Of course, I know about Imagine Breaker, too.
もちろん 幻想殺し(イマジンブレイカー)についても
まあ 超能力者のカリキュラムを
受け過ぎたせいで―
But yeah, having gone through a lot of the
esper curriculum, much of my magic is unusable now.
魔術のほうは
使えなくなっちまったけどな
Either way, there is a high probability that
the spellcaster of Angel Fall is hiding near you.
（神裂）
とにかく
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)を発動させた術師は―
あなたの近くに
潜んでいる可能性が高い
儀式場についても しかり
The same could apply to the ritual location.
We should move together for now and investigate the enemy's objective and their next move.
ここは しばらく行動を共にし
敵の目的 および 出方を
探らせてもらいます
Do you have any objections, Misha Kreuzhev?
異存はありませんか？
ミーシャ＝クロイツェフ
Answer no. 1 - That should be the most intelligent strategy.
（ﾐｰｼｬ）
回答１
それが最も賢明な策だと思われる
W-Wait!
ちょ… ちょっと待ってくれよ
I'm with family members that I haven't seen in a while.
俺は今
久しぶりに家族と一緒にいるんだ
旅館には 俺の両親やいとこが…
My parents and cousin are at the hotel-
Do your parents and cousin appear like they should to you?
その両親やいとこが あなたには
しかるべき姿に見えていますか？
不幸だ
Such misfortune.
ンッ…
なにがお守りだ　ふざけやがって
Some charm you are.
Piece of shit!
（土御門）
レプリカにも力が宿るんだぜ
Replicas have some power enchanted in them, too, y'know?
The basic principle in idol worship.
偶像崇拝の基本ぜよ
To think that you're a magician...
（上条）
お前が魔術師だとはな
（土御門）
正確には“だった”　過去形だにゃ
"Were", it's past tense now.
風水を専門とする―
The best Onmyo professor of Necessarius who specialized in Feng Hsui is now just a plain old human.
必要悪の教会(ネセサリウス)きっての陰陽(おんみょう)博士も
今じゃ すっかり ただの人
（上条）
みんなの所には行かないのか？
You're not going to join the others?
（土御門）
行きたくても 行けないにゃ
I wish I could, but I can't.
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)が発動したとき
When Angel Fall was activated, Kanzaki-neechin and I cast seals on ourselves right away,
俺と神裂ねーちんは
とっさに結界を張ったんだが
完全には しのぎきれなかった
but we couldn't get away from it completely.
From the eyes of everyone that "switched sides",
入れ替わった人たちからすると
I'm Hitotsui Hajime apparently.
この俺は
一一 一(ひとつい はじめ)に見えるらしいぜよ
Hitotsui Hajime?
一一 一(ひとつい はじめ)？
（上条）
…て あのチャラいアイドルか？
You mean, that shallow idol?
それなら 神裂は…
Then, who's Kanzaki...
My... Touma's friends are really unique.
（刀夜(とうや)）
いやぁ　当麻の友達は
本当にユニークな人ぞろいだ
（美琴(みこと)）
…ていうか おにいさん カッコイイ
Oniisan, you're so cool!
Red hair and a cigarette in your mouth...
真っ赤な髪に
くわえタバコだなんて
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
しかも 頬っぺにバーコード
And a bar code on your cheek!
How do you say this again...
何ていったかしら ほら…
You want to say he's dandy, right, Aunt Shiina?
（美琴）
イケてるって言いたいんでしょう？
詩菜(しいな)おばさん
My, my~
（刀夜）
そうだ
君たちにエジプト土産のお守りを
Oh that's right.
Here's a charm from Egypt for you all-
（琴美）
もう！　スカラベなんかやめてよ
刀夜おじさん
Forget the scarabs, Uncle Touya!
Hey, by the way.
（刀夜）
ああ　ところで 君
名前は何といったかな？
What was your name again?
ンッ…　神裂です
Kanzaki...
ステイルだって？　そりゃいいや
She's Stiyl?
That's a good one.
あっ お前 さっき
結界張ったって言ったよな？
Wait, you just said you cast a seal, right?
超能力者に魔術は使えないんじゃ…
Aren't espers unable to use magic?
ああ　だから 体はボロボロだぜ
Yeah, that's why I'm messed up all over.
If I use magic again,
もっかい魔術使ったら
血管が破裂して ボーン
my blood vessels will burst, and *bang*
I'll be dead for sure.
（土御門）確実に死んじまうわな
（上条）アア…
そうそう カミやん
お前の“不幸だ”って口癖
Oh, that's right, Kami-yan.
Your "such misfortune" favorite phrase,
ねーちんの前では
ちっとばかし自粛してくれないか？
try not to say it in front of Neechin.
（上条）うん？
（土御門）ねーちんは不幸の逆
Opposite to your misfortune,
Neechin is a person that can't tolerate her own fortune.
自分の幸運が
許せないでいる人だからにゃ
Can't tolerate her own fortune?
幸運が許せない？
日本には“天草(あまくさ)式”っていう―
In Japan, there's an organization called Amakusa-shiki, founded by Christians hiding in Japan.
隠れ十字教が作った組織が
あるんだが
It was determined that Kanzaki-neechin was to be the top of that organization, the Priestess, at birth.
神裂ねーちんは
生まれつき そこのトップ
女教皇(プリエステス)になることが決まっていた
She's one of only a few "Saints" in this world capable of wielding a Stigma.
世界に数えるほどしかいない
聖痕(スティグマ)使いの聖人だ
“聖人” これ すなわち
“神の子の力を宿せる人間”
A Saint, in other words, a human that can harness the power of the son of God.
聖痕(スティグマ)を解放した場合
When she unleashes her Stigma, Neechin is able to temporarily wield power greater than that of humans.
ねーちんは一時的に
人間を超えた力を使うことができる
そんなすんげえ星のもとに生まれた
自分の幸運が許せないんだと
She apparently can't forgive herself for being born with that much fortune and blessing.
やれやれ… また神さまか
Great, "God" again?
And why is that a worry for her?
…で なんで
そんなもんが悩みになるんだ？
こればっかりは
当人じゃないと分からない
That's something only she would know.
But, Kami-yan.
けど カミやん
幸運なヤツってのは
どんな気持ちなんだろうな
How do fortunate people feel?
（土御門）
常に たった１本しかない
当たりくじを―
To always be drawing the one and only winning lottery ticket...
引いてしまうってことは―
...means you're always going to have others draw the losing tickets.
周りに
絶対にハズレを引かせちまうんだぜ
ハァ… もう耐えられません
I can't take it anymore.
（神裂）
実は私 その…
To tell the truth, I...
...because of the effects of Angel Fall...
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)の影響で…
聞いたよ
ステイルに見えるんだろう？
So I heard, your appearance is Stiyl, right?
そうです
That is correct.
入浴して
疲れを癒やしたいのですが
I'd like to take a bath to relieve my fatigue,
but if someone comes in while I'm in the ladies' bath, panic will ensue.
女湯に入っていて
誰かが来たら一大事
ああ　男湯に誰かが入ってきても
困るってことか
And you also have a problem if someone goes into the men's bath, too?
だから
ここで見張っていてほしいのです
So, please stand watch for me here.
To make sure no one comes in.
誰も入ってこないように
Are we clear?
いいですね？　頼みましたよ
I've asked you this favor.
ハァ…
不幸だ
Such misfortune.
あっ おっと… こいつは
神裂の前では禁句だったな
Oh, right. It's a taboo phrase in front of Kanzaki.
当麻　こんな所にいたのか
Touma, there you are.
（上条）父さん？
（刀夜）ちょうど良かった
Dad?
Perfect timing.
Let's go take a bath together, father and son, like old times.
久しぶりに 親子水入らずで
ひとっ風呂 浴びようじゃないか
あっ ちょっと待った！
今はダメだ　中に人が入ってる
W-Wait!
Not now!
Someone's inside!
What's wrong with that?
それが どうした？
温泉なんだから 当たり前だろう
It's a hot spring; that's normal.
（上条）
いや… だから その…
No, it's umm...
フフッ… 水くさいヤツだな
Don't be so bashful.
What's there to be embarrassed, we're grown men.
（刀夜）
男同士 何を恥ずかしがってるんだ
Ah- That is- Really... It's okay...
（上条）えっと…
（刀夜）やあ
Umm...
Hey, red-haired, cigarette-chewing, bar-code cheeked Kanzaki-kun!
真っ赤な髪に くわえタバコに
バーコードな神裂君じゃないか
（神裂）
…たく
Gosh!
（土御門）
裸を見られたくらいで
恩を忘れるのかにゃ？
Forgetting your gratitude just because he saw your naked body?
カミやんは インデックスの命を
救った恩人なんだぜ
Kami-yan is the one we are indebted to for saving Index's life.
感謝こそすれ 風呂場から
たたき出すってのは ちょっとにゃ
Thank him, we should,
but chasing him out of the bath area, I wonder...
I understand it well.
（神裂）
分かっています そんなこと
分かってはいるのですが
I understand, but...
（刀夜）
ハァ… いやぁ お前の友達は
まったくもってユニークだ
Man, your friend is really, really unique.
For him to be panicking so much even though we're all men.
男同士なのに
あんなにも取り乱すなんて ハァ…
（上条）
これには いろいろと事情が…
There's a lot of reasons behind this.
事情？
まさか彼は そっち系の人で―
Reasons?
Don't tell me he really swings "that" way,
that he can't marry anymore because I saw his naked body?
私に裸を見られた以上
もはや お嫁になるしかないと？
拾えねえ飛躍してんじゃねえよ
そうじゃなくて…
Stop fantasizing about things the wrong way already.
That's not it-
そっか　御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)で みんなの
見た目が入れ替わったってことは…
That's right...
That everyone's appearance has switched due to Angel Fall...
...means that the appearance of Dad
is really the face of some stranger.
父さんのこの姿も 本当は
どっかの知らないおっさんなんだ
うん？　どうした？
急に しょんぼりして
What's wrong?
You seem all depressed all of a sudden.
何でもないよ
It's nothing.
その顔 母さんに そっくりだ
That face of yours looks just like your mother's.
結婚前 デートを重ねていたころ
Before we got married, when we were having dates every now and then,
as the time came for us to part ways,
別れの時間が近づいてくると
母さんは決まって そんな顔をした
your mother would always have that look on her face.
それを見るのが つらくて…
And I couldn't bear seeing that...
また いとおしくてね
...but I found it so darling, as well...
お前は やっぱり母さん似だ
You take after your mother more after all.
あっ そうだ
そんなお前にメキシコ土産の…
Oh right, here's a souvenir from Mexico-
要らねえよ！
I don't want it!
Hm, that's...
（刀夜）うん？　あれは…
（上条）うん？
（上条）
ミーシャ…
Misha.
うん…
あどけない幼顔に浮かぶ あの憂い
The gloominess on such an innocent child's face.
まるで声をかけてと
言わんばかりじゃないか
It's like she wants us to talk to her.
Touma, good luck!
当麻　グッドラック
Huh? Hey!
えっ？　おい！ …たく
Geez...
（上条）
何してるんですか？
What are you up to?
え～ 遠くロシアは
ツンデレの大地に思いをはせて―
Are you a bit homesick since Russia, the land of Tsundere, is so far away?
Note: This is a pun on Tundra (tsundora) and Tsundere
ホームシックとか？
ツッコミが入らねえ
She's not responding to the joke!
Does this woman understand the emptiness when a joke gets ignored?!
スルーされたボケが
どんだけ惨めか
この女 分かってねえ！
（上条）
食うか？
Want one?
Did you find out anything about Angel Fall?
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)について 何か分かった？
あのさ 天使が どうとか
俺には よく分からないけど
You know, I don't understand much about this angel business,
犯人は なんで また―
but why did the suspect activate this kind of spell to begin with?
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)なんて魔術を
発動させたりなんかしたんだ？
私見１
莫大(ばくだい)な天使の力を手に入れるためか
Hypothesis no. 1 - To acquire the vast amount of power an angel possesses?
Or to become part of the angel class?
あるいは
自らが天使の位に居座るためか
（ﾐｰｼｬ）御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)は未完成
（上条）えっ？　そうなのか？
Angel Fall is incomplete.
Huh? Really?
（ﾐｰｼｬ）
天使の力は たったひとりで
バチカンを壊滅させるほど
The power of an angel is strong enough to destroy the Vatican.
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)が完成したら…
If Angel Fall were completed,
世界に神話規模の厄災が起きる
a calamity as great as those of lore would take place.
（上条）あっ…
（ﾐｰｼｬ）その前に術者を特定し―
We must identify the spellcaster before that and prevent the completion of the spell.
なんとしても
完成を阻止しなければ
R-Right.
そ… そうだな
This isn't the time to be chewing on gum, huh?
ガムなんか食ってる場合じゃ
なかったな　悪い
My bad.
World crisis?
世界の危機…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）あらあら 刀夜さん
（上条）うん？
My, my, Touya-san.
Hold on.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
ちょっと…
あら　刀夜さん的には―
My, what are you getting all energetic about, Touya-san?
何をそんなに
元気になっているのかしら
（刀夜）
当麻の顔を見ていたら
なんだか昔を思い出してね
Seeing Touma's face brought back a lot of memories, you see.
And I thought he'd like a brother or sister.
いやぁ… それに
あいつも 弟か妹が欲しかろうと
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あらあら　そうかしら？
My, my, is that so?
あっ！　ミーシャ 悪い
Sorry, Misha.
Before the world's crisis,
世界の前に
俺には差し迫った危機があったわ！
I have to take care of another, personal one right now!
（ドアの開く音）
（上条）ちょっとストップ！
Stop!
ストップ ストップ！
Stop! Stop!
（刀夜）
あっ！　当麻 なんてところに…
Touma?!
What time are you barging in-
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あらあら　当麻さん的には
久しぶりに 家族一緒に寝たいのね
My, my, Touma-san, you want to sleep together with the whole family again, huh?
Okay, let us sleep like the "Kawa" kanji tonight.
Note: Kawa - Where the child (shortest stroke) sleeps in between the two parents (longer strokes)
いいわ
今日は３人 川の字で寝ましょう
Touma! Touma!
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
当麻！　当麻！
当麻がお部屋にいないんだよ！
Touma's not in his room!
He hasn't come back since last night!
昨日の夜から
帰ってないみたいなんだよ　当麻！
Touma-
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）あらあら 大変！
（刀夜）どうした 母さん！
My, my, oh no!
What's wrong, Mom?
（上条）
…んだよ？　朝っぱらから
慌ただしいな
What's going on; it's still so early...
Everyone's in such a haste...
当麻…
Touma...
（刀夜）
何をそんなに急いでるんだ？
Why are you in such a hurry?
I forgot to lock the front door.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
玄関の鍵を
かけ忘れてきちゃったんです
行って 戸締まりしてきますわ
I'll go back and lock up.
電車で往復だと 丸１日かかるぞ
It'll take a whole day there-and-back by train.
I'll be back by evening.
夕方までには帰りますから
Question no. 1 - May I accompany you?
（ﾐｰｼｬ）問１
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）うん？
（ﾐｰｼｬ）同行してもかまわないか？
（上条）ミーシャ…
Misha?
Repeating question no. 1 - May I accompany you?
問１をもう一度
同行してもかまわないか？
My, my, Misha-chan. You want to give me some company along the way?
あらあら　ミーシャちゃんったら
私の話し相手に
なってくれるのかしら
Okay, let's go together.
いいわ　一緒に行きましょう
Why does Misha have to accompany Ind- Mom?
なんだって また
ミーシャがインデ… 母さんと
（刀夜）うん？　読めたぞ 当麻
（上条）うん？
I see how it is, Touma.
You were her first, Touma.
彼女は お前が初めてだったのさ
“これは もう
お嫁になるしかない”と―
That's why she has to become your bride now...
...and she's trying to score points with her future mother-in-
今から 嫁姑(よめしゅうとめ)の確執を防ぐべく…
What are you talking about?!
なにワケ分かんないこと
言ってんだよ！
フフッ… 昨日は なかなか
いいムードだったじゃないか
You two were in a good mood last night, weren't you?
You were peeking, you perverted father!
…て のぞいてやがったのか？
この変態親父(おやじ)！
Heck, if you were watching, couldn't you tell?
つうか
見てたんなら 分かってんだろう
フフッ… 冗談だよ 冗談
I'm just kidding, okay?
しかし 今どき 珍しいくらい
奥ゆかしい子だ
But she's a rather modest girl; a rarity these days.
She tried not to touch your hand at all.
何しろ お前の手に
触れようともしないんだから
うん？　手？
Hand?
My... right hand...
俺の右手…
（ﾐｰｼｬ）
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)は未完成
Angel Fall is incomplete.
完成したら
世界に神話規模の厄災が起きる
If Angel Fall were completed,
a calamity as great as those of lore would take place.
Misha said that?
（神裂）
ミーシャが そんなことを？
（上条）
なあ　御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)ってのの実態は―
Hey, so we don't really know
the actual form of Angel Fall, right?
よく分かってないんだよな？
（神裂）
はい
Correct.
There isn't even a record in the British Library,
英国図書館の記録にも
記載されていない未知の現象ぜよ
a completely unknown phenomenon.
So, how does she know if such a thing is incomplete or not?
そんなもんが未完成だって
なんで分かるんだ？
完成したら 厄災が起きるって
That a calamity would occur if it were completed...
...why is Misha able to say that?
どうして
ミーシャに言い切れるんだ？
ミーシャは
なぜ俺の右手に触れなかった？
Why did Misha not touch my right hand?
Just because she was a bit shy?
単に恥ずかしいからか？
それとも…
Or...
...she cast the spell herself...
（土御門）
自らが発動させ…
現在も進行中の御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)を
打ち消されたくなかった？
...and didn't want the in-progress spell of Angel Fall to be erased...
Kami-yan! Take us to your home!
（土御門）カミやん　家に案内しろ
（上条）おう！
Okay!
Hmm? A map to our home?
うん？　家の地図？
We moved, right?!
引っ越したんだろう？
新しい家の地図を描いてくれ
Draw me a map to our new home!
（刀夜）
急に どうしたんだ？
母さんなら 別に追わなくたって…
Why all of a sudden?
You don't have to go after Mom or anything.
（刀夜）読めたぞ 当麻
（上条）読まんでいい！
I see how it is, Touma!
Don't!
さては 母さんに
ミーシャちゃんを奪われるのが…
You don't want Mom stealing Misha-chan away from you-
（上条）
そういう拾いづれえ飛躍はいいから
Quit fantasizing in such an unreasonable fashion,
and hurry!!!
（上条）早く！
（刀夜）分かった 分かった
All right, all right.
Assuming Misha cast Angel Fall,
（上条）
ミーシャが
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)を発動させたとして
why is she after Index, I mean, Mom?
なんでインデックスに…
母さんについていったんだ？
さあな
Beats me.
We'll need to ask Misha personally to find out.
こればっかりは ミーシャに
直接 聞いてみないと分からんぜよ
This... is my home?
ここが俺の家…
Mom! Misha!
母さん！　ミーシャ！
それじゃ
ここで ご到着を待つとするぜよ
Let's wait for their arrival here.
（土御門）
あっ… おい カミやん
Hey, Kami-yan!
…たく
Geez.
親父のお土産マニアぶりも
筋金入りだな
Dad sure goes crazy in his souvenir mania.
Nothing here either.
ここにも…
Kamijyo Touma
It's... my name...
俺の名前…
I don't remember anything after all...
やっぱ 何にも思い出せねえや
What's the matter, Tsuchimikado?
どうした？　土御門
なるほど
そういうことだったとはな
I see.
So that's how it is.
（上条）
うん？　これが どうかしたのか？
What's wrong with this?
（土御門）
触るな
Don't touch it!
Hey, what's going on, Tsuchimikado?
（上条）
おい　どうしたんだよ？　土御門
I said, hey!
おいって… あっ…
This... is my mother...
これが 俺の母さん
Huh?
あれ？　父さん
Dad?
This was a photo from New Year last year.
（美琴）
去年のお正月の写真だよ
Do you remember me now, Touma-oniichan?
これで私のこと思い出してくれた？
当麻お兄ちゃん
This one, too.
これも
こっちも
And this one.
Dad's appearance didn't get switched?!
父さんは入れ替わってない？
土御門　これって…
Tsuchimikado, this...
The only person that isn't affected by Angel Fall, besides exceptions like you, Kami-yan...
御使堕し(エンゼルフォール)の影響を受けないのは―
カミやんみたいな例外を除いて
ただ１人
...is the spellcaster himself.
魔術を発動させた術師だけぜよ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あらあら　まあ 大変！
My, my.
Oh, no.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
まあ！　一一 一(ひとつい はじめ)！
My, Hitotsui Hajime!!!
I don't know what you're doing here,
どうして ここにいるのか
知らないけれど
But I'm a big fan of yours!!!
私的には
あなたの大ファンなのよ！
（土御門）カミやん 追え！
（上条）えっ？
Kami-yan, after her!
（土御門）
お前を犯人だと思ったミーシャが
何をしようとしたか忘れたのか？
You forgot what Misha tried to do to you when she thought you were the culprit?!
Why, Dad?
なんでだよ？　父さん
How come you're able to do something like this?!
（上条）
なんで あんたに
そんなことができるんだよ？
Why did you put your hands into the occult world?
なんでオカルトなんかに
手ぇ出したんだよ？
（姫神(ひめがみ)）
危ねえじゃねえか こら！
死にてえのか！
Watch where you're going, damn it!!!
You wanna die or somethin'?!
ひ… 姫神？
Hi-Himegami?!
Get outta the way already!
さっさと どけや！
ひき殺すぞ オンドリャー！
Or I'm gonna flatten 'ya!
（姫神）
あっ …んだ？ てめえ
What the-
乗っけてください　お願いします
Give me a ride.
Please!
…んだと？　これのどこが
タクシーに見えんだ こら！
Say what?!
Does this look like a damn taxi cab to you, huh?!
Dad's... My father's life is in danger!
親父の…
（上条）父さんの命が危ないんです
（姫神）なに？
What?
I want to save my father!
父さんを助けたいんです！
助けなきゃいけないんです
I need to...
I beg you!
頼みます！
ク～ッ！　なんだよ
泣かせてくれるじゃねえか
This brings me to tears, yo!
A child who pays tribute to his parents is so rare these days!
今どき 親孝行な息子だねえ
All right!
おっしゃ！　いいから
早いとこシートベルトしな！
Buckle up right now!
振り落とされても知らねえぞ！
I won't pick you up if you get thrown out of the window, eh?
（姫神）
オラオラ オラオラァ！
Outta the way, damn it!
Move it, move it, move it, move it!!!
Where's Dad?
Where's Misha?
（神裂）ミーシャは？
（上条）父さんは？
Hey, where's Dad?!
なあ　父さんは どこだ？
ミーシャは？
Where's Misha?!
彼女は あなたたちが
追っていったのではありませんか
Didn't you two go after her?
刀夜氏なら 海岸に
Mr. Touya is on the beach.
What exactly is the matter?
一体 どうしたのです？
I see.
（神裂）
そうでしたか
あなたは
ここで待っていてください
You must wait here.
This is my job now.
ここから先は 私の仕事
I will secure Mr. Touya's-
（神裂）刀夜氏の身柄は 私が…
（上条）お断りだ
I don't think so.
I'll take matters into my own hands.
こいつは俺が決着をつける
（神裂）しかし…
（上条）“しかし”じゃねえ
But-
No buts!
Kamijyo Touya is my father!
上条刀夜は俺の父さんなんだ！
My one and only... father...
（上条）
俺の たったひとりの
父さんなんだよ
Dad.
（上条）
父さん
～♪
Next Episode
The emergence of a terrible entity that surpasses the world of human knowledge,
（上条）
人智を超えた恐るべき存在の出現
a power that's set out to destroy the world,
世界を滅ぼさんとする その力に
立ちはだかる神裂
and Kanzaki, who is standing against it.
そして 土御門は…
And Tsuchimikado...
Next time, "The Power of God".
次回 「大天使(かみのちから)」
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる
When science and magic cross paths,
this epic will begin!